<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--Credit to Gabriele Mariotti for the ChangeLog Library:-->
<!--https://github.com/gabrielemariotti/changeloglib-->
<changelog bulletedList="false">
    <changelogversion versionName="Aug 10, 2024" changeDate="">
        <changelogtext>[b]This is the final update for World Scribe for Android.[/b] It is with a
            heavy heart that we announce that further development of the official World Scribe
            Android app will be ceasing after this update. World Scribe began as a simple hobby
            project in 2016. At the time, we decided the app would use simple text files in external
            storage so that World data could be easily copied over to another device, or even edited
            in other apps. However, recent changes in Android 13 have severely limited access to
            external storage. As a result, World Scribe's core functionality is no longer compatible
            with Android. Making the app work with Android 13+ would require a rewrite of the app,
            and for a free project that we built in our spare time, this is not something that we
            can pursue at this time due to other life commitments. But that doesn't mean World
            Scribe is going away completely! We have also released [b][a href="https://worldscribe2.averistudios.com/"]World Scribe 2[/a][/b],
            a successor to World Scribe that you can use on your desktop PC. If you have an older
            Android device and would still like to use the Android app, you can download the APK
            installation files [b][a href="https://github.com/MarquisLP/World-Scribe/releases"]here[/a][/b].
            If you are an Android developer, feel free to fork the [b][a href="https://github.com/MarquisLP/World-Scribe"]source code repository[/a][/b]
            and develop your own version of World Scribe. [b]If your device is on Android 13 or
            later and the app is no longer working for you, you can recover your World data by
            searching for a "WorldScribe" folder in your device's file storage.[/b] Thank you so
            much for all of your support over the years, and we hope you continue to broaden the
            limits of imagination through world-building.
        </changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>
    <changelogversion versionName="Dec 23, 2020" changeDate="">
        <changelogtext>[b]Performance issues on Android 10 and above have been fixed![/b] A large
            portion of the app was rewritten to make navigation faster and prevent the app from
            freezing. Thank you for your patience in waiting for this update. Because this is a large
            update, you may encounter errors. If you do, please let us know in an email, with
            screenshots if possible, at: support@averistudios.com
        </changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>
    <changelogversion versionName="Nov 15, 2020" changeDate="">
        <changelogtext>[b]Please be aware that if you upgrade your device to Android 10 or Android
            11, the app may perform significantly slower.[/b] This is due to changes by Google in
            the Android operating system that make file operations much slower. We are currently
            working to improve this situation, but we ask that you please be patient as this will
            require significant changes throughout the entire app. We deeply apologize to users who
            are already impacted by these performance issues.
        </changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>
</changelog>
