<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--Credit to Gabriele Mariotti for the ChangeLog Library:-->
<!--https://github.com/gabrielemariotti/changeloglib-->
<changelog bulletedList="true">
    <changelogversion versionName="1.6.1" changeDate="Feb 29, 2020">
        <changelogtext>[b]The official developer website for Averi Studios is live![/b] You can
            access it from within the app by opening the menu in the top-right and selecting 'Developer
            'Website'. Check it out to keep up with important announcements and our other projects.</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]Alphabetical sorting is now in place for lists of Connections, Memberships,
            Members, Residences, and Residents.[/b] This keeps things consistent and makes it easier
            for you to find what you're looking for in those lists.</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]The full changelog has now been translated into German![/b] [i]Thank you to
            tostc for this contribution.[/i]</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]Crashes during storage location selection have been fixed![/b] However, if
            you're still encountering crashes or other issues, please don't hesitate to reach out to
            us at averistudios@gmail.com.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>
    <changelogversion versionName="1.6.0" changeDate="Jan 9, 2020">
        <changelogtext>Major changes have been made under-the-hood in order to comply with new
            Android policies. The app might take more time to open pages, particularly if your device
            runs Android 10 or above. We apologize for any inconvenience, but unfortunately, Android's
            new policies have made it so that our only option was a major code rewrite.
            The app has been tested thoroughly to ensure that everything behaves exactly the same as
            before. However, if you encounter any bugs, please don't hesitate to email us about it at:
            averistudios@gmail.com</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>You can now backup Worlds to NextCloud! To do so, open the menu on the
            top-right and select 'Backup to NextCloud'. [i]Thank you to tostc for this contribution.[/i]</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>Some issues in the German translation have been fixed.
            [i]Thank you to tostc for this contribution.[/i]</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>
    <changelogversion versionName="1.5.1" changeDate="Dec 7, 2019">
        <changelogtext>[b]German language support has been added![/b] The app's language will
            automatically switch if you have a German locale set as your primary in your device's
            system settings. [i]Thank you to tostc for this contribution.[/i]</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]Faster and smoother scrolling in the Snippet page.[/b] Now you can reach
        the bottom of a Snippet with just a flick of your thumb!</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]Bugfix: deleted folders for Connections, Snippets, and other sub-Article
            elements no longer cause errors.[/b] If you have a cleaning app, it may delete empty
            folders on your device. Prior to this update, this would cause problems, as a deleted
            Connections folder (for example) would prevent the app from making new Connections to
            an Article. With this update, those folders will automatically be recreated, so you
            don't have to worry about disabling or uninstalling anything in your cleaning apps.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.5.0" changeDate="Aug 13, 2019">
        <changelogtext>[b]A new theme has been added: Chrome Gray![/b] Try combining it with
            Night Mode for a slick visual experience.</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]Menus have been reorganized![/b] By popular demand, [b]the 'Delete World'
        option has been moved to the Settings page[/b], so now you won't have to worry about
        accidentally deleting your creations. World-related options have also been removed from
        Article pages in order to reduce clutter.</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]Text and icons have been shrunken down to better scale with your device's
        font settings.[/b] Look at all the extra space you have to work with now! If you preferred
        the larger text size from previous versions, you can change it back via the font settings
        in your device's system settings.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.4.7" changeDate="Jan 13, 2019">
        <changelogtext>Want to help us make future versions of World Scribe even
            better? [b]You can now fill out the user survey [a
            href="https://goo.gl/forms/3VAhRuAajgBKmXyY2"]here[/a]![/b]
            You can also access the survey by opening the overflow menu on the top-right and
            selecting "Feedback".</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.4.6" changeDate="Aug 25, 2018">
        <changelogtext>[b]Fixed one of the Dropbox issues![/b] This one was caused
            by an invalid Dropbox "access token" (a small record stored on your
            device that tells Dropbox your account info is valid). If you were one
            of the users affected by this issue, then when you try to upload again,
            the app will ask you to reauthenticate. If you do so, then the old
            access token will be replaced by a new one, allowing you to upload your
            Worlds without any further problems.</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]Some major behind-the-scenes improvement to how
            Dropbox uploading works.[/b] As a user, you won't see much of a
            difference, but rest assured the new uploading method is more robust and
            should make problems less likely and easier to troubleshoot in the
            future.</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]More Dropbox bug fixes to come![/b] The fix above doesn't
            apply to all errors that users have sent in. If you are still facing
            Dropbox issues after this update, please be patient as we work on
            a resolution. In the meantime, you can help us out by trying to upload,
            and then sending the error log when prompted.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.4.5.a" changeDate="Aug 19, 2018">
        <changelogtext>[b]Added more Dropbox error logging improvements.[/b] We will continue
            to release logging improvements until the Dropbox upload issue has been resolved, so
            please try to keep the app updated. Again, if you are still experiencing issues with
            Dropbox uploading, please try to upload again, and then send the error log when
            prompted. Thank you for your co-operation.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.4.5" changeDate="Aug 15, 2018">
        <changelogtext>[b]Improved error logging for Dropbox issues.[/b] If you are
            experiencing issues with uploading to Dropbox, please try uploading again,
            and then send the error log when prompted. The sooner we can identify
            what is causing this issue, the sooner we can fix it.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.4.4" changeDate="Jul 17, 2018">
        <changelogtext>[b]Improved security in order to comply with F-Droid policies.[/b] The app
            will soon be available on F-Droid!</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.4.3" changeDate="Jul 15, 2018">
        <changelogtext>[b]Fixed the bug that prevented some users from uploading to Dropbox.[/b]
        Apologies for any inconvenience this bug may have caused. If problems still
        persist, please contact us at: [i]averistudios@gmail.com[/i]</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.4.2" changeDate="Apr 20, 2018">
        <changelogtext>[b]Fixed a bug that prevented Dropbox error logging from working
            correctly on some devices.[/b] For more info on Dropbox error logging,
            see the notes for version 1.4.1.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.4.1" changeDate="Apr 18, 2018">
        <changelogtext>
            [b]Error reporting has been added for Dropbox issues.[/b] We are aware that
            certain users have been unable to backup their Worlds to Dropbox. We're looking to
            implement a fix for this problem ASAP, but first we need your help to gather more
            info on this bug. [b]If you've been unable to backup to Dropbox, please follow these
            steps:[/b] open the overflow menu, select 'Backup World to Dropbox' and wait for the
            error message to appear. Make sure 'Send error log via email' is checked, then tap 'OK'.
            Select the email app of your choice, then send the email that appears. (No need to edit
            anything or add a description.) Thank you for your co-operation!
        </changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.4.0" changeDate="Dec 24, 2017">
        <changelogtext>[b]Bug fix: images used in this app will no longer appear in the Gallery app.
            [/b] Sorry for any inconvenience this bug may have caused! [i]If images still appear
            in the Gallery, try restarting your device. If the issue still persists even after
            that, please send an email to averistudios@gmail.com containing your device model
            and Android version.[/i]</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]Reader Mode has been added![/b] While browsing an Article
            or Snippet, you can tap the glasses icon at the top of the screen to
            disable text input, making for a smooth reading experience without
            worrying about the keyboard coming up as you scroll. To go back to
            editing, simply tap the keyboard icon.</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]World/Article/Snippet names have been marquee'd![/b] If
            a name is too long to fit onto the screen, the text will
            automatically scroll to show you the full title. Rejoice, long name
            enthusiasts![/b]</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]Bug fix: all 'Rename' dialogs now have the proper dark background color
            when Night Mode is enabled[/b] (rather than white)</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.3.3" changeDate="Aug 28, 2017">
        <changelogtext>[b]Fixed a bug that prevented images from being uploaded to Dropbox.[/b]</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]Added a confirmation message that appears when trying to upload a World to
            Dropbox.[/b]</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]Darkened the background colour in Night Mode.[/b] For all fans of "Ube
            Purple"
            and "Lovely Red", rejoice -- you no longer have to squint at your text in the dark!</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.3.2" changeDate="Jul 1, 2017">
        <changelogtext>[b]Updated to the latest Dropbox SDK[/b] in order to avoid a
        bug with the older SDK version.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.3.1" changeDate="Apr 30, 2017">
        <changelogtext>[b]Fixed a bug that would cause Article images to clutter up the Gallery
            app.[/b] Sorry for any inconvenience this may have caused! [i]Note:
            this fix didn't work. The proper solution was implemented in 1.4.0.[/i]</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.3.0" changeDate="Dec 24, 2016">
        <changelogtext>[b]Dropbox backup support has been added![/b] While browsing Articles,
            choose "Backup to Dropbox" from the menu to upload the current World to your Dropbox
            account.</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]The bottom navigation bar has been significantly improved![/b]
            Its smaller and sleeker appearance is easier on the eyes, and frees up screen
            real-estate for your all-important world content.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.2.0" changeDate="Dec 16, 2016">
        <changelogtext>[b]Fixed a significant bug that would cause the app to crash in several
            places due to missing folders.[/b] Sincerest apologies to the (many) users who have
            experienced this issue!</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]Added searching for Articles by Category![/b] Just tap on the magnifying
            glass icon while browsing through Articles, or while choosing an Article to link.</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]When choosing an Article to link, the Articles are now sorted
            alphabetically.[/b]</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.1.1" changeDate="Sep 30, 2016">
        <changelogtext>[b]Fixed a bug that prevented the most recently opened world from
            automatically opening on startup, if that world was renamed during the previous session.
            [/b]</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]World renaming has been added![/b] Settle for any name now, and let the
            perfect moniker come to you later.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion versionName="1.0.1" changeDate="Sep 5, 2016">
        <changelogtext>[b]Fixed a bug that would cause devices with Android API 21 or lower to crash
            upon opening the "Create Article" screen.[/b]</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

</changelog>
